{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084118405","data":{"timestamp":" 947084118405"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084124549","data":{"timestamp":" 947084124549"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084131093","data":{"timestamp":" 947084131093"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084136772","data":{"timestamp":" 947084136771"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-body.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084146996","data":{"timestamp":" 947084146996"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084152075","data":{"timestamp":" 947084152074"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.body.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084162386","data":{"timestamp":" 947084162386"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..22.off2.17__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084170652","data":{"timestamp":" 947084170652"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084189227","data":{"timestamp":" 947084189227"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 60f7f370-bcd0-4b9c-bf1f-bdc37d7979e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" meno_goti-sikio-pua-meno"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" meno"," userResponse":" meno"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084194347","data":{"timestamp":" 947084194347"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 60f7f370-bcd0-4b9c-bf1f-bdc37d7979e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" jicho_jicho-mkono-vidole-sikio"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jicho"," userResponse":" jicho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084198326","data":{"timestamp":" 947084198326"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 60f7f370-bcd0-4b9c-bf1f-bdc37d7979e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" goti_pua-goti-ndevu-mkono"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" goti"," userResponse":" goti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084205238","data":{"timestamp":" 947084205238"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 60f7f370-bcd0-4b9c-bf1f-bdc37d7979e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" kichwa_kichwa-mkono-sikio-tumbo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kichwa"," userResponse":" kichwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084206968","data":{"timestamp":" 947084206968"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 60f7f370-bcd0-4b9c-bf1f-bdc37d7979e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" kichwa_kichwa-mkono-sikio-tumbo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" kichwa"," userResponse":" tumbo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084207402","data":{"timestamp":" 947084207401"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 60f7f370-bcd0-4b9c-bf1f-bdc37d7979e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" nywele_goti-nywele-meno-pua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nywele"," userResponse":" pua"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084207993","data":{"timestamp":" 947084207993"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 60f7f370-bcd0-4b9c-bf1f-bdc37d7979e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" nywele_goti-nywele-meno-pua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" nywele"," userResponse":" pua"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084208367","data":{"timestamp":" 947084208367"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 60f7f370-bcd0-4b9c-bf1f-bdc37d7979e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" nywele_goti-nywele-meno-pua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" nywele"," userResponse":" pua"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084208392","data":{"timestamp":" 947084208392"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 60f7f370-bcd0-4b9c-bf1f-bdc37d7979e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" nywele_goti-nywele-meno-pua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" nywele"," userResponse":" pua"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084211257","data":{"timestamp":" 947084211257"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 60f7f370-bcd0-4b9c-bf1f-bdc37d7979e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" nywele_goti-nywele-meno-pua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 5"," expectedAnswer":" nywele"," userResponse":" nywele"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084217201","data":{"timestamp":" 947084217201"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 60f7f370-bcd0-4b9c-bf1f-bdc37d7979e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" mkono_mkono-kichwa-goti-vidole"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mkono"," userResponse":" vidole"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084219558","data":{"timestamp":" 947084219557"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 60f7f370-bcd0-4b9c-bf1f-bdc37d7979e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" mkono_mkono-kichwa-goti-vidole"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" mkono"," userResponse":" mkono"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084223871","data":{"timestamp":" 947084223871"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 60f7f370-bcd0-4b9c-bf1f-bdc37d7979e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" tumbo_mdomo-pua-ngumi-tumbo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tumbo"," userResponse":" tumbo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084231082","data":{"timestamp":" 947084231082"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 60f7f370-bcd0-4b9c-bf1f-bdc37d7979e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" mdomo_mkono-nywele-mdomo-bega"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mdomo"," userResponse":" mdomo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084235144","data":{"timestamp":" 947084235144"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 60f7f370-bcd0-4b9c-bf1f-bdc37d7979e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" tumbo_tumbo-mikono-nywele-pua"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tumbo"," userResponse":" tumbo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084239091","data":{"timestamp":" 947084239090"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 60f7f370-bcd0-4b9c-bf1f-bdc37d7979e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" meno_vidole-meno-sikio-pua"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" meno"," userResponse":" meno"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084241058","data":{"timestamp":" 947084241054"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 60f7f370-bcd0-4b9c-bf1f-bdc37d7979e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" meno_vidole-meno-sikio-pua"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084256034","data":{"timestamp":" 947084256034"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" aebba436-a641-4492-8de0-a71ff013f210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" meno_vidole-meno-sikio-pua"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" meno"," userResponse":" meno"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084260064","data":{"timestamp":" 947084260064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" aebba436-a641-4492-8de0-a71ff013f210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" mkono_mkono-kichwa-goti-vidole"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mkono"," userResponse":" mkono"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084265760","data":{"timestamp":" 947084265760"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" aebba436-a641-4492-8de0-a71ff013f210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" tumbo_tumbo-mikono-nywele-pua"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tumbo"," userResponse":" tumbo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084271306","data":{"timestamp":" 947084271306"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" aebba436-a641-4492-8de0-a71ff013f210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" tumbo_tumbo-nywele-ndevu-vidole"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tumbo"," userResponse":" tumbo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084275668","data":{"timestamp":" 947084275668"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" aebba436-a641-4492-8de0-a71ff013f210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" meno_goti-sikio-pua-meno"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" meno"," userResponse":" meno"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084279940","data":{"timestamp":" 947084279940"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" aebba436-a641-4492-8de0-a71ff013f210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" goti_pua-goti-ndevu-mkono"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" goti"," userResponse":" goti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084284263","data":{"timestamp":" 947084284263"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" aebba436-a641-4492-8de0-a71ff013f210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" tumbo_mdomo-pua-ngumi-tumbo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tumbo"," userResponse":" tumbo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084291290","data":{"timestamp":" 947084291290"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" aebba436-a641-4492-8de0-a71ff013f210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" kichwa_kichwa-mkono-sikio-tumbo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kichwa"," userResponse":" kichwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084299583","data":{"timestamp":" 947084299583"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" aebba436-a641-4492-8de0-a71ff013f210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" mguu_meno-mguu-goti-tumbo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mguu"," userResponse":" mguu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084305227","data":{"timestamp":" 947084305226"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" aebba436-a641-4492-8de0-a71ff013f210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" body_1"," problemName":" meno_mguu-meno-goti-kichwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" meno"," userResponse":" meno"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:body","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084307217","data":{"timestamp":" 947084307216"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" aebba436-a641-4492-8de0-a71ff013f210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" meno_mguu-meno-goti-kichwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084312357","data":{"timestamp":" 947084312356"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" aebba436-a641-4492-8de0-a71ff013f210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_body"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" meno_mguu-meno-goti-kichwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084324365","data":{"timestamp":" 947084324364"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Simo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084324828","data":{"timestamp":" 947084324828"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Simo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084325078","data":{"timestamp":" 947084325078"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Simo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084325601","data":{"timestamp":" 947084325600"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Simo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMO"," userResponse":" SIMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084328533","data":{"timestamp":" 947084328533"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Simo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084330218","data":{"timestamp":" 947084330218"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Simo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084333505","data":{"timestamp":" 947084333505"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Simo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084335752","data":{"timestamp":" 947084335751"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Simo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084338281","data":{"timestamp":" 947084338281"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nina marifiki wanne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084339277","data":{"timestamp":" 947084339277"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nina marifiki wanne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIFIKI"," userResponse":" MARIFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084339989","data":{"timestamp":" 947084339989"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nina marifiki wanne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANNE"," userResponse":" WANNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084342921","data":{"timestamp":" 947084342921"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nina marifiki wanne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084355004","data":{"timestamp":" 947084355003"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nina marifiki wanne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084357244","data":{"timestamp":" 947084357244"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nina marifiki wanne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANNE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084359621","data":{"timestamp":" 947084359621"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Majina yao ni Zizo Lele Sisa na Ayanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJINA"," userResponse":" MAJINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084360075","data":{"timestamp":" 947084360075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Majina yao ni Zizo Lele Sisa na Ayanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084360258","data":{"timestamp":" 947084360258"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Majina yao ni Zizo Lele Sisa na Ayanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084361072","data":{"timestamp":" 947084361071"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Majina yao ni Zizo Lele Sisa na Ayanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIZO"," userResponse":" ZIZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084361995","data":{"timestamp":" 947084361995"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Majina yao ni Zizo Lele Sisa na Ayanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LELE"," userResponse":" LELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084362949","data":{"timestamp":" 947084362949"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Majina yao ni Zizo Lele Sisa na Ayanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISA"," userResponse":" SISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084363422","data":{"timestamp":" 947084363422"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Majina yao ni Zizo Lele Sisa na Ayanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084364109","data":{"timestamp":" 947084364109"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Majina yao ni Zizo Lele Sisa na Ayanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AYANDA"," userResponse":" AYANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084370951","data":{"timestamp":" 947084370951"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Majina yao ni Zizo Lele Sisa na Ayanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084385111","data":{"timestamp":" 947084385111"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Majina yao ni Zizo Lele Sisa na Ayanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084387038","data":{"timestamp":" 947084387038"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Majina yao ni Zizo Lele Sisa na Ayanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084395280","data":{"timestamp":" 947084395280"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Majina yao ni Zizo Lele Sisa na Ayanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIZO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084398294","data":{"timestamp":" 947084398294"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Majina yao ni Zizo Lele Sisa na Ayanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LELE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084409405","data":{"timestamp":" 947084409403"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Majina yao ni Zizo Lele Sisa na Ayanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084409559","data":{"timestamp":" 947084409559"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Majina yao ni Zizo Lele Sisa na Ayanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LELE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084453856","data":{"timestamp":" 947084453856"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 71aa689d-e384-4988-9620-d4c3fc9b9c86"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Majina yao ni Zizo Lele Sisa na Ayanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084488417","data":{"timestamp":" 947084488417"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 07a7e899-ea93-43eb-9384-00d6d5d2c2ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chura"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chu"," userResponse":" chu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084503954","data":{"timestamp":" 947084503954"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 07a7e899-ea93-43eb-9384-00d6d5d2c2ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_chura"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084518922","data":{"timestamp":" 947084518922"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 81845acf-d78e-4927-9b78-6e9a0ed25197"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mboga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbo"," userResponse":" mbo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084523667","data":{"timestamp":" 947084523667"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 81845acf-d78e-4927-9b78-6e9a0ed25197"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mboga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084528482","data":{"timestamp":" 947084528482"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 81845acf-d78e-4927-9b78-6e9a0ed25197"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_lamba"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084534694","data":{"timestamp":" 947084534694"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 81845acf-d78e-4927-9b78-6e9a0ed25197"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_lamba"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084535610","data":{"timestamp":" 947084535610"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 81845acf-d78e-4927-9b78-6e9a0ed25197"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_lamba"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084539186","data":{"timestamp":" 947084539186"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 81845acf-d78e-4927-9b78-6e9a0ed25197"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pini"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084540115","data":{"timestamp":" 947084540115"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 81845acf-d78e-4927-9b78-6e9a0ed25197"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pini"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084558405","data":{"timestamp":" 947084558405"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 81845acf-d78e-4927-9b78-6e9a0ed25197"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_watu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084559296","data":{"timestamp":" 947084559296"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 81845acf-d78e-4927-9b78-6e9a0ed25197"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_watu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tu"," userResponse":" tu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084562921","data":{"timestamp":" 947084562921"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 81845acf-d78e-4927-9b78-6e9a0ed25197"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kaka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084563444","data":{"timestamp":" 947084563444"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 81845acf-d78e-4927-9b78-6e9a0ed25197"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kaka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084566966","data":{"timestamp":" 947084566966"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 81845acf-d78e-4927-9b78-6e9a0ed25197"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nzi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084568493","data":{"timestamp":" 947084568492"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 81845acf-d78e-4927-9b78-6e9a0ed25197"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nzi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zi"," userResponse":" zi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084571165","data":{"timestamp":" 947084571165"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 81845acf-d78e-4927-9b78-6e9a0ed25197"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_gogo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084572072","data":{"timestamp":" 947084572072"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 81845acf-d78e-4927-9b78-6e9a0ed25197"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_gogo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084575546","data":{"timestamp":" 947084575546"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 81845acf-d78e-4927-9b78-6e9a0ed25197"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jembe"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" je"," userResponse":" je"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084576503","data":{"timestamp":" 947084576503"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 81845acf-d78e-4927-9b78-6e9a0ed25197"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jembe"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084579718","data":{"timestamp":" 947084579717"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 81845acf-d78e-4927-9b78-6e9a0ed25197"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kundi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084580900","data":{"timestamp":" 947084580900"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 81845acf-d78e-4927-9b78-6e9a0ed25197"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kundi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndi"," userResponse":" ndi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084586341","data":{"timestamp":" 947084586341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 81845acf-d78e-4927-9b78-6e9a0ed25197"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mbuni"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbu"," userResponse":" mbu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084587338","data":{"timestamp":" 947084587338"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 81845acf-d78e-4927-9b78-6e9a0ed25197"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mbuni"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084589144","data":{"timestamp":" 947084589143"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 81845acf-d78e-4927-9b78-6e9a0ed25197"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_mbuni"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084602289","data":{"timestamp":" 947084602289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 0d6d9071-e8c3-4c5b-99e6-f8dcc321d44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuku"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084603786","data":{"timestamp":" 947084603786"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 0d6d9071-e8c3-4c5b-99e6-f8dcc321d44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuku"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084607320","data":{"timestamp":" 947084607320"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 0d6d9071-e8c3-4c5b-99e6-f8dcc321d44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hoho"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ho"," userResponse":" ho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084608217","data":{"timestamp":" 947084608217"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 0d6d9071-e8c3-4c5b-99e6-f8dcc321d44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hoho"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ho"," userResponse":" ho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084611009","data":{"timestamp":" 947084611009"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 0d6d9071-e8c3-4c5b-99e6-f8dcc321d44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_gari"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084611681","data":{"timestamp":" 947084611681"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 0d6d9071-e8c3-4c5b-99e6-f8dcc321d44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_gari"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084614515","data":{"timestamp":" 947084614515"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 0d6d9071-e8c3-4c5b-99e6-f8dcc321d44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mboga"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbo"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084615271","data":{"timestamp":" 947084615271"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 0d6d9071-e8c3-4c5b-99e6-f8dcc321d44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mboga"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" mbo"," userResponse":" mbo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084616221","data":{"timestamp":" 947084616221"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 0d6d9071-e8c3-4c5b-99e6-f8dcc321d44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mboga"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084619121","data":{"timestamp":" 947084619121"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 0d6d9071-e8c3-4c5b-99e6-f8dcc321d44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuni"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084619827","data":{"timestamp":" 947084619827"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 0d6d9071-e8c3-4c5b-99e6-f8dcc321d44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuni"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084622983","data":{"timestamp":" 947084622983"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 0d6d9071-e8c3-4c5b-99e6-f8dcc321d44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nyama"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nya"," userResponse":" nya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084623924","data":{"timestamp":" 947084623924"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 0d6d9071-e8c3-4c5b-99e6-f8dcc321d44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nyama"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084626642","data":{"timestamp":" 947084626642"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 0d6d9071-e8c3-4c5b-99e6-f8dcc321d44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mama"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084627623","data":{"timestamp":" 947084627623"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 0d6d9071-e8c3-4c5b-99e6-f8dcc321d44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mama"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084630449","data":{"timestamp":" 947084630449"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 0d6d9071-e8c3-4c5b-99e6-f8dcc321d44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_njiwa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nji"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084631087","data":{"timestamp":" 947084631087"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 0d6d9071-e8c3-4c5b-99e6-f8dcc321d44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_njiwa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" nji"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084637217","data":{"timestamp":" 947084637217"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 0d6d9071-e8c3-4c5b-99e6-f8dcc321d44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_njiwa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" nji"," userResponse":" nji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084638316","data":{"timestamp":" 947084638316"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 0d6d9071-e8c3-4c5b-99e6-f8dcc321d44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_njiwa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084641577","data":{"timestamp":" 947084641577"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 0d6d9071-e8c3-4c5b-99e6-f8dcc321d44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_dobi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" do"," userResponse":" do"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084642665","data":{"timestamp":" 947084642665"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 0d6d9071-e8c3-4c5b-99e6-f8dcc321d44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_dobi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bi"," userResponse":" bi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084646265","data":{"timestamp":" 947084646265"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 0d6d9071-e8c3-4c5b-99e6-f8dcc321d44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jasho"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084647153","data":{"timestamp":" 947084647153"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 0d6d9071-e8c3-4c5b-99e6-f8dcc321d44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jasho"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sho"," userResponse":" sho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084649129","data":{"timestamp":" 947084649128"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 0d6d9071-e8c3-4c5b-99e6-f8dcc321d44e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_jasho"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084667003","data":{"timestamp":" 947084667003"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" e9fa7d84-8137-4e81-9b1a-7684fb9ec9ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuku"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084669766","data":{"timestamp":" 947084669765"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" e9fa7d84-8137-4e81-9b1a-7684fb9ec9ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuku"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084692030","data":{"timestamp":" 947084692029"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" e9fa7d84-8137-4e81-9b1a-7684fb9ec9ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_kuku"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084699151","data":{"timestamp":" 947084699151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" e9fa7d84-8137-4e81-9b1a-7684fb9ec9ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_kuku"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084724430","data":{"timestamp":" 947084724430"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ziwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zi"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084730935","data":{"timestamp":" 947084730935"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ziwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" zi"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084737674","data":{"timestamp":" 947084737673"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ziwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" zi"," userResponse":" zi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084738531","data":{"timestamp":" 947084738531"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ziwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084741439","data":{"timestamp":" 947084741439"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chombo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cho"," userResponse":" cho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084741746","data":{"timestamp":" 947084741746"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chombo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbo"," userResponse":" mbo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084744855","data":{"timestamp":" 947084744855"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_watu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" tu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084745777","data":{"timestamp":" 947084745777"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_watu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084746585","data":{"timestamp":" 947084746585"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_watu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tu"," userResponse":" tu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084749842","data":{"timestamp":" 947084749841"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ua"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084750525","data":{"timestamp":" 947084750525"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ua"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084751526","data":{"timestamp":" 947084751526"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ua"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084754410","data":{"timestamp":" 947084754410"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mbuni"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbu"," userResponse":" mbu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084754806","data":{"timestamp":" 947084754806"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mbuni"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084758080","data":{"timestamp":" 947084758080"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mboga"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbo"," userResponse":" mbo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084758562","data":{"timestamp":" 947084758562"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mboga"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084761729","data":{"timestamp":" 947084761729"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chu"," userResponse":" chu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084762169","data":{"timestamp":" 947084762169"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngwa"," userResponse":" ngwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084766218","data":{"timestamp":" 947084766218"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zizi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zi"," userResponse":" zi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084766699","data":{"timestamp":" 947084766699"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zizi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zi"," userResponse":" zi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084769664","data":{"timestamp":" 947084769664"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mende"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" nde"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084770747","data":{"timestamp":" 947084770747"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mende"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084771497","data":{"timestamp":" 947084771497"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mende"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nde"," userResponse":" nde"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084774238","data":{"timestamp":" 947084774238"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_lima"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084775036","data":{"timestamp":" 947084775036"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_lima"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084775661","data":{"timestamp":" 947084775661"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_lima"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084777682","data":{"timestamp":" 947084777681"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_lima"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947084784897","data":{"timestamp":" 947084784897"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_175503"," gameId":" 02d9682f-4791-4e09-b4b8-5dcd20c76523"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_lima"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}